listen up you crushed it 200 Sales
okay so here's the big
surprise I want 200 more sales by 8:00
tonight is he serious dude like
exhausted now he wants us to work late
you want to go home and you want to rip
farts and watch the Dome the door is
right there but if you want to be a
phone beast and you want to be rewarded
that's right rewarded we're going to
have Botox shots flying around the
office as well as Sushi strippers for
all you boys and
girls okay right Showdown Tokyo yeah
heck yeah if you guys get to 200 Sales
400 total for tonight you get to whee
the juice with the Weez man
himself
Poli oh my God man what up
T van eyes guys who who's ready to
Mother
party me I am Paulie me and Paulie are
old friends and uh he lost a
bet this makes us even JP you son of a
yeah well if you guys start
working the phones and you start making
those sales guess what I'll get you on
TMZ tonight
yes wish I would have had some beers in
here some maybe that saki bombs or
something some of that Sushi man it's
one of those hot little stripper
[Music]
I'm
fresh you got you got got got to be
fresh